gagein.com 2014-12-16

# Gagein | The New Standard for B2B Prospecting

Gagein (“Gagein”) has created this privacy policy (the “Policy”) so you will understand when and how personal and business information is collected, used, disclosed and protected with respect to your use of our Website (“Site”) located at [http://www.gagein.com](http://www.gagein.com/).

We reserve the right to change this privacy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our home page. By continuing to use the Gagein service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on the Gagein website, you are consenting to the changes.

###### Personal Information Collection

The purpose of the Gagein website is to allow Gagein users (“Users”) to voluntarily provide information about themselves and their businesses for the purposes of building, maintaining and enhancing a business network to discover business opportunities and achieve business goals. You willingly provide us certain personal and business information, which we collect in order to allow you to benefit from the Gagein website. If you have any hesitation about providing such information to us and/or having such information displayed on the Gagein website or otherwise used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, you should not become a member of the Gagein community.

We collect your personal and business information in the following ways:

###### Registration

When you register an account to become User, we may collect various kinds of contact information about you including, for example, your name, business you work for, title, job level, job function, office city, country, state and e-mail address. We may also collect business information that you provide to us. Finally, you will also be asked to create a user-chosen ID and password for your use when accessing the Service.

###### Profile Information

Once you become a User, you may provide additional information in “My Profile” such as Department, Office Address, and Zip Code. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration to become a User is entirely optional, but enables you to better identify yourself and find new opportunities in the Gagein system to build and leverage your business network. Any information you provide at registration or in the “My Profile” section that is not personally identifiable may be used in the same manner and extent to which other information that is not personally identifiable is permitted to be used.

###### Contact Information

In order to invite others to connect with you directly in Gagein, you may use the Gagein services to invite them if they are a User, or enter their names and email addresses. This information will be used by Gagein to send your invitation including a message that you write. The names and email addresses of people that you invite will be used only to send your invitation and reminders.

You may also choose to manually enter or upload data about your contacts into the private “Connections” section of the Gagein website. You may not invite anyone to connect with you whom you do not know. All information entered there will only be viewable by you and will not be searchable by others in the Gagein network without your permission. All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as cover your own information.

###### Submissions and Use of Services and Interactive Areas of Site

Personal information may also be collected if you provide additional information while using or interacting with the Site, or otherwise participate in interactive areas on the Site or using the Service. This may include business-related information (such as Business, Industry, Sub Industry, Business Description, Public/Private, HQ Address, HQ City, HQ Country, HQ State, Zip Code, Revenue Size, Employee Size, website, URLs), as well as access control configurations, or when Users opt to submit news articles and news links for your businesses.

###### Automatically Collected Information

We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you use the Service, our systems may automatically collect your IP address and the type of operating system or browser you use. We may also collect information pertaining to your account activity, information pertaining to the files accessed or used by you, transactional information, information on the content you post, and standard access information, such as the time and date of accessing the Service, and usage of the Service. We use such information to help customize the Site and the Service, and to manage the effectiveness of our marketing effort. We may also correlate this information with personal information through the use of backend analytical tools, and may use telephone numbers to perform reverse directory look-ups. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is not shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

###### Consent to Gagein Processing Information About You

Please be aware that in providing information to Gagein for the purposes of opening your user account, you are expressly and voluntarily accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and Gagein’s User Agreement. The supplying of all such information by you to Gagein, including all information deemed “sensitive” by applicable law, is entirely voluntary on your part. You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time, in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, but please note that your withdrawal of consent will not be retroactive.

###### Cookies

We may also use cookie technology to collect information. Among other things, the use of cookies enables us to improve our Site by seeing which areas and features are most popular; to count the number of computers accessing the Site; to personalize the Site and improve the Site experience; to potentially record your preferences and track the ads you view; and to allow you to visit the Site without re-entering your member ID and/or password. A cookie is a small amount of data, often including an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Most browsers automatically accept cookies as the default setting. You can modify the setting to reject cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit by editing browser options. However, if a browser is set not to accept cookies or if a user rejects a cookie, some portions of the Site and the Service may not function properly. For example, you may not be able to sign in and may not be able to access certain Site features or services.

###### Web Beacons

“Web beacons” (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags, single-pixel GIFs, clear GIFs, invisible GIFs, 1-by-1 GIFs, and web bugs) are tiny graphic files placed on a Web page which send a signal when a user has visited that page, allowing the site to collect standard access information, such as time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides. We use web beacons to help manage the effectiveness of our online advertising and to gather access information, such as counting the users who have visited those pages and compiling aggregated statistics about site usage; our web beacons do not contain any personal information and we do not link web beacons to personal information about you.

###### Rights to Access, Correct and Eliminate Information About You

You have a right to access, modify, correct and eliminate the data about you which has been collected pursuant to your decision to become a User. If you update any of your information, we may keep a copy of the information which you originally provided to us in our archives for uses documented herein.

We take your rights seriously and encourage you to use them if you deem this to be appropriate. You may exercise these rights by emailing us at [info@gagein.com](mailto:info@gagein.com).

###### Customer Service

Gagein may collect information through the Gagein website in order to, among other things, accurately categorize and respond to a client’s inquiry and deliver appropriate service levels.

###### Uses of Personal Information

Gagein is an online service dedicated to helping business people stay on top of business news of the businesses they follow and connect with each other more effectively. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on our website is used to help you describe yourself to other Users. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by Gagein from Users (such as, for example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by Gagein. This information can be utilized by Gagein in such manner as Gagein, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

###### Gagein Communications

Gagein will communicate with you through email and notices posted on the Gagein website or through other means available through the service, including text and other forms of messaging. If we send any communications to you via the carrier service with which you have a mobile communications subscription or otherwise have access, you understand you will pay any service fees associated with any such access (including text messaging charges for messages to your mobile device). Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from Gagein related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another User in your network sends you an opportunity.

###### Customized Content

Information provided to Gagein (or to third parties with whom it offers combined services) is also used to customize your experience on our website. For example, when you login to your account we will display the businesses you are following and the news updates of those businesses.

###### Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except (i) when we have your permission, (ii) to third party service providers who need access to such information to carry out their work for us, (iii) as part of a business transfer, (iv) when required by law or permitted to protect our rights, property, or safety; or (v) as otherwise described in our Privacy Policy. The following section describes these disclosure circumstances more fully.

    * Consent. Unless you give us your consent, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. With your consent, we may disclose your personal information to third parties so that they may provide you with products and services that you have requested.

    * Public Profile. Gagein offers a “Public Profile” feature which allows Users to publish their Gagein profile, including their “name”, but not their “email address” or “phone number” to the public Internet. Users may opt-out of this feature by checking the “Opt Out” box in “Profile” tab in “Settings.” Gagein does not warrant how often third-party search engines will update their cache.

    * Aggregated Anonymous Data. We may provide aggregated anonymous data about the usage of our services to third parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate, including to prospective advertisers on Gagein. We may segment our Users by role (i.e. product managers, vice presidents), industry, geographic location, or business. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our Users” activities on the site, please email [info@gagein.com](mailto:info@gagein.com).

    * Service Providers. We may share personal information with third party vendors, consultants, and other service providers who assist us in operating and managing the Site, the Service or our business and who need access to such information to carry out their work for us. For example, we may share your personal information with companies who are fulfilling orders, processing payment or other information, or administering contests or surveys on our behalf. We may also share personal information with service providers who are performing internal analysis of the Site on our behalf, such as to estimate our audience size, measure aggregate traffic patterns as well as to understand demographic, client interest, and other trends among our users. In the event that we use third party vendors to assist us in performing these functions, the third parties may not use or disclose your personal information for any other purpose.

    * Business Transfers. Information about our users and the Service is one of our most important business assets. Therefore, information about our users, including personal information, may be disclosed and transferred as part of any merger or acquisition, creation of a separate business to provide the Service or fulfill products, sale or pledge of company assets as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company.

    * Protection of Gagein and Others. We may release personal information in the good faith belief that release is appropriate and necessary to comply with legal process or authority (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply our policies; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our rights, property, or personal safety of Gagein, our users, our employees, or the public; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay. We will notify you before disclosing your information for purposes of responding to legal process.

    * Submissions and Posting on Public Areas of the Site. You understand that when you make Submissions or post news or news link on public areas of the Site, information you include in such Submissions or postings may be publicly available to users of The Site and other services such as search engines or third-party partner sites that can access public information on the Site. We recommend you be cautious about posting personal information in Submissions or in postings on public areas of the Site. We are not responsible for the actions of any third parties with whom you share personal information.

###### Communications to other Users

Many emails you initiate through Gagein, e.g., an invitation sent to a non-User, will list your email address and name in the header of the message. Emails you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network (for instance how many businesses you are following and how many people are in your network), but will not list the people to whom you’re directly connected. Other communications that you initiate through the Gagein website, like a request for contact, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another User if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other.

###### Legal Disclaimer

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, such as responses to civil or criminal subpoenas, or other requests by law enforcement personnel. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, subpoena, or other legal process or request to Gagein brought in any country throughout the world, or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

###### Disclosures to others

We may also disclose your personal and other information you provide, to another third party as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets of a Gagein corporation division or company. Any third party to which we transfer or sell Gagein’s assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us.

###### 2\. Important Information

###### Access and Control of Personal Information

If you are a registered user of our Service, you may view, correct, and delete your personal information simply by logging into your account. Generally, you should be careful when making any personal information available to the public.

Users may “opt in” or “opt out” to receive marketing or promotional communications or solicitations from Gagein on our behalf or on behalf of third parties. Users may also “opt in” or “opt out” of receiving communications directly from third parties. However, this shall not affect our ability to send you service and account related emails or to use your personal information as otherwise described in this Policy.

###### Closing Your Account

You can also close your account through the Gagein website. If you close your Gagein account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable database. We may retain certain data contributed by you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the Gagein website, please send your request to [info@gagein.com](mailto:info@gagein.com). Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with Gagein under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to [info@gagein.com](mailto:info@gagein.com) within five business days of its receipt.

###### Your Obligations

As a User, you have certain obligations toward the other Users with whom you will be communicating. Certain of these obligations are imposed by applicable law and regulations, and others have become commonplace in user-friendly communities like Gagein:

    * You must, at all times, respect the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and the User Agreement.                                                

    * You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information which may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic or which may otherwise violate the purpose and spirit of Gagein and its community of Users.

    * You must not provide information to Gagein and /or other Users which you believe might be injurious or detrimental to your person, professional or social status.

    * Gagein has also self-certified its privacy practices as consistent with U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor principles: Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Access and Accuracy, Security, Data Integrity and Enforcement. More information about the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program can be found at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account by Gagein, as we take these principles seriously and consider them to be the basis on which our Users adhere to the Gagein website and the services offered.

###### Children

Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not use Gagein services.

###### Security

In order to secure your personal information, access to your data on Gagein is password-protected, and sensitive data is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged between your web browser and the Gagein web site. To protect any data you store on our servers we also regularly audit our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and we use a tier-one secured-access data center. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information. Please note that emails and instant messaging and similar means of communication with other users of Gagein are not encrypted and we strongly request you not to communicate any confidential information through these means.

###### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Gagein may update this privacy policy at any time, with or without advance notice. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on the Gagein website or send you an email, as provided for above. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

If you use the Gagein service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

###### California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code section 1798.83 permits clients who are California residents to request certain information regarding disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not provide your personal information to any third party for their direct marketing purposes without your consent. If you would like more information with respect to your privacy rights under California law, you may contact us at the contact point below. Please reference your request as “California Disclosure Information.”

###### International Users

By using our Site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of Gagein, we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. Please note that your personal information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your country. If you object to your personal information being transferred or used as described in this Policy, please do not register for the Service.

###### How to Contact Us

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at [info@gagein.com](mailto:info@gagein.com) or contact us by mail at:  
Gagein, Inc.   
2077 Gold Street, Suite 208  
San Jose, CA 95002
